* 
        
    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 

    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 

    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 

    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 

    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 

    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 

    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 

    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 
        
    * 

FAMILY OWNED BUSINESS

|

HASSLE-FREE EXCHANGES

|

FREE SHIPPING OVER $49

|

PRICE MATCH GUARANTEE

Privacy Policy
==============

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the [Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/details.html) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._  
  
**My Cooling Store** PRIVACY PLEDGE  
  
At MyCoolingStore.com, we recognize and respect the importance of maintaining the privacy of our customers and have established this Privacy Policy as a result. Below we describe why we gather customer information, what information we collect, how we collect it, and how we use this information.  
  
**Why do we gather information?** Since our inception, MyCoolingStore.com has consistently provided our customers with quality products and superior customer service. We gather personal information to allow us to successfully process your orders, to provide a personalized shopping experience and to inform you of special promotions and discounts.  
  
**What information do we gather?** When you order from our web site, we collect the following information: your name, telephone number, email address, billing information (credit card number, expiration date and billing address), products purchased, any relevant promotion code and the recipient's name, address and telephone number.  
  
**How do we use the information we collect about you?** We use information we collect from you to process your orders, to provide a more personalized shopping experience and to inform you of offers and discounts. We do not make your email addresses available to third parties.  
  
**Your Consent and Changes to this Policy:** Subject to the above provisions, by using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by us and the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time and we will post those changes so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it.  
  
**How payments are processed:** Your credit card payments are securely processed through Pay Pal�. You do not need to have a Pay Pal� account to make a purchase. This offers you the confidence of knowing your information is being handled by the most respected name in online transactions.  
  
**Your Comments:** We welcome feedback concerning this Privacy Policy. Please send your comments and questions.  

Join our mailing list today and be the first to hear all about the latest news, promotions and offers from My Cooling Store!

Copyright 2022: JustBrand Limitetd / All Rights Reserved
